so it can't be real yeah you know that
kind of exactly exactly so my other
buddy his Grand Oh I thought we were
going to oh no no no no that's cool
leave it in I'll just show what we got
here oh okay you know and uh yeah so
anyways tell me about how much you
increased your fuel mods is really this
is a testimony I want this St he came
over to get some saw parts and have his
a saw fixed and uh it was about it was
put a wire in this car here probably
about 200k about 200k on what increase
yeah increase sweet man sweet that's
awesome no I'm glad I could help so what
we do here is we take this wire and we
bear about 5
in on it of just copper wire we get rid
of the rubber boot and we get it as deep
into the water as we can and this is the
same Principle as a Joe cell you excite
the water molecules as the water is
running through the block it excites the
water molecules ejects electrons now the
positive ions and this battery will
start to draw out the freed electrons
these batteries will increase in voltage
you'll see water drifting out your
tailpipe you'll increase your fuel
mileage right have you seen any of that
oh yeah first thing you think is your
your your uh head gas gets blown yeah
exactly that too or uh your your gas
gaug is busted right I mean that's I've
seen that it's typical and uh so what
yeah so these batteries gaining
voltage I don't know it's it's pretty
simple but he's leaking a bit but he's
leaving it and he's just keeping an eye
on his temperature making sure he's not
going to it up and uh I don't know
if I can put that on YouTube but
whatever whatever but it works oh hey
what you say it works oh yeah 100% and
have you met me before we did this
before we don't know each other no no no
no you you know you're a young fellow
that I just saw I'd share some
information with pretty much yeah
cool so anyways yeah one wire from there
to the negative on the battery that's it
that's all you got to do now if you got
uh anything after 83 when they well they
started putting oxygen sensors in the
Volvo in the 70s but most of them are
after 83 you can't do it because it'll
increase your fuel Ms cuz I or'll give
you more yeah decrease cuz cuz this the
oxygen sensor won't recognize the CO2
coming out because this energy actually
fights with that and it actually helps
clean some of that up too it does like
you if you did admission test before and
after you'd see it's way cleaner too
just with this one wire yeah I'm going
to do it on my this is real people and
uh do you mind if I put you on film
Stanton no that's fine Stanton is this
real it's definitely real all right
thanks Budd appreciate it okay